|Anele Maseko| IT Graduate

☐ anelemaseko5@gmail.com GITHUB: https://github.com/AneleMaseko

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anele-maseko-0763b2224

Ebony Park, Midrand 1632

0761378804

PROFILE

Recent graduate with a National Diploma in Information Technology (Software Development) and a passion for Information Technology it can be from Software Development, Cloud Computing etc. SDLC, with Experience in Manual Testing and a little bit of Automation Testing.

EDUCATION

Jerusalem sec School | White River

Jan 2009-2013

Subject Passed: English, SiSwati, Mathematics, Physical Science, Life Sciences, Geography Life Orientation

Tshwane University of Technology | Pretoria

Jan 2017-Sept 2022

National Diploma in IT Software Development

Key Modules: Communication Networks, Technical Programming, IT Mathematics, Data analysis, Structured Query languages

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Participated in a hackathon for CapaCiti (2023).
- Did an online application website for a school at CapaCiti (2023). https://singular-jellya85453.netlify.app/
- Did an online application website for a school at Adom Technologies (2022). https://gns-admin2f230.web.app/index.html
- Did an e-commerce website project for the school (2021).
- Class monitor in High School (2013).

SOFT SKILLS

Languages: English (*Fluent*), SiSwati (*Fluent*), Sepedi (*Fluent*), Zulu (*Fluent*) Strong work ethic and ability to function well in a team.

Excellent time management, Problem Solver Good interpersonal skills, Analytical thinking Work well under pressure and meet deadlines. Self-Motivation, drive and energy Continuous passion for learning Team working skills, Multitasking.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C++, JIRA, Python, Java, PHP, C#, React, node.js, Jira, Git and GitHub, PhpMyAdmin (Basics), Linux (Basics), Remote Support(AnyDesk), Agile, Syncfussion and Tailwind CSS.

Experience

Adom Technologies | Nelspruit

Aug 2022-Jul 2023

WIL Program: Software Development Key

Developing Softwares.

Upgrading of software.
Database management.

CapaCiti / UVU Africa | Johannesburg

Aug 2023- present

Internship: Software Development/ Tester/DevOps *Key Responsibility*

- Software Development.
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO).
- Continuous Integration and continuous delivery.
- Familiar with Git, GitHub, and Docker.
- Developed and Executed test cases.
- Manual Testing.

Skills: Git and GitHub, JIRA, JavaScript, HTML, Python, Java, SQL, Linux and React, Syncfusion, Tailwind CSS.

References

Adom Technologies: mentor | MR Chris Sifundza

Position: Senior Software developer

Contacts: 073 614 4461

GNS: mentor | Mr Brian Mkasi

Position: Support Manager/ Project Manager

Contacts: 079 598 8633.